voxilla.com 2011-12-16

# Privacy Policy

Voxilla knows that how personal information is gathered, used and shared is very important to you, and we appreciate the trust you put in us. We tell you just how we do those three things in our privacy policy. You accept this policy when you visit Voxilla.

### What Personal Information Does Voxilla Gather?

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continuously improve your experience at Voxilla.  
Here are the types of information we gather:

  * **Information You Give Us:** We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, improving our content, tools, product offerings and website, and communicating with you.
  * **Automatic Information:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use cookies, and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Voxilla.

### What’s Up With Cookies?

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that Voxilla transfers to your computer hard drive through your Web browser to allow our systems to recognize your browser and to provide personalized logins. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to enjoy a convenient and enriched shopping experience so we recommend that you leave them turned on. 

### Does Voxilla Share the Information It Receives?

Voxilla is not in the business of selling its information to others. We share customer information only as described below:

  * **Agents:** We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include processing credit card payments. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
  * **Third Party Advertising** : We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/pdfs/NAI_principles.pdf). Google is a third-party vendor that uses cookies to serve ads on Voxilla.com. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Voxilla.com readers based on their visits to Voxilla and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
  * **Protection of Voxilla and Others:** We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Voxilla, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice. Under no circumstances will Voxilla share any account or personal information with a government agency without an appropriate court order.

### How Secure Is Information About Me?

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

### Self-Identifying Information

You provide such information when you search, buy or communicate with customer service. For example, you provide information when you place an order through the Voxilla Store; provide information in Your Account (and you might hav more than one if you have used more than one e-mail address when registering with us); communicate with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone numbers; credit card information; people to whom purchases have been shipped, including addresses and phone number; and product preferences.

### Automatic Information

Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; purchase history, the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; products you viewed or searched for. During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.

  * [](http://twitter.com/intent/tweet?text=Privacy%20Policy%20-%20http%3A%2F%2Fvoxilla.com%2Fvoxilla%2Fprivacy-policy%20\(via%20@sociablesite\) "Twitter")
  *
